{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947796080752","data":{"timestamp":" 947796080752"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" d9b76f84-87de-4b65-8ad0-4ac55ed816b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947796082757","data":{"timestamp":" 947796082757"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" d9b76f84-87de-4b65-8ad0-4ac55ed816b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947796085779","data":{"timestamp":" 947796085779"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" d9b76f84-87de-4b65-8ad0-4ac55ed816b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947796087397","data":{"timestamp":" 947796087397"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" d9b76f84-87de-4b65-8ad0-4ac55ed816b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947796090001","data":{"timestamp":" 947796090001"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" d9b76f84-87de-4b65-8ad0-4ac55ed816b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947796091933","data":{"timestamp":" 947796091933"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" d9b76f84-87de-4b65-8ad0-4ac55ed816b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947796092721","data":{"timestamp":" 947796092721"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" d9b76f84-87de-4b65-8ad0-4ac55ed816b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947796092804","data":{"timestamp":" 947796092804"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" d9b76f84-87de-4b65-8ad0-4ac55ed816b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947796096802","data":{"timestamp":" 947796096802"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" d9b76f84-87de-4b65-8ad0-4ac55ed816b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947796103786","data":{"timestamp":" 947796103785"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" d9b76f84-87de-4b65-8ad0-4ac55ed816b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..25.off2.18__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947796110312","data":{"timestamp":" 947796110312"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" d9b76f84-87de-4b65-8ad0-4ac55ed816b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947796120352","data":{"timestamp":" 947796120323"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" d9b76f84-87de-4b65-8ad0-4ac55ed816b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947796126269","data":{"timestamp":" 947796126268"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" d9b76f84-87de-4b65-8ad0-4ac55ed816b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947796132173","data":{"timestamp":" 947796132173"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" d9b76f84-87de-4b65-8ad0-4ac55ed816b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947796138719","data":{"timestamp":" 947796138719"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" d9b76f84-87de-4b65-8ad0-4ac55ed816b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947796146397","data":{"timestamp":" 947796146396"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" d9b76f84-87de-4b65-8ad0-4ac55ed816b0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801364274","data":{"timestamp":" 947801364274"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e5ce8b1b-2ec2-450a-b63d-7ee713170281"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801364497","data":{"timestamp":" 947801364497"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e5ce8b1b-2ec2-450a-b63d-7ee713170281"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801365461","data":{"timestamp":" 947801365461"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e5ce8b1b-2ec2-450a-b63d-7ee713170281"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801366734","data":{"timestamp":" 947801366734"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e5ce8b1b-2ec2-450a-b63d-7ee713170281"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801367021","data":{"timestamp":" 947801367021"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e5ce8b1b-2ec2-450a-b63d-7ee713170281"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801367093","data":{"timestamp":" 947801367093"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e5ce8b1b-2ec2-450a-b63d-7ee713170281"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801377405","data":{"timestamp":" 947801377404"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e5ce8b1b-2ec2-450a-b63d-7ee713170281"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:9..29.off2.19__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801384115","data":{"timestamp":" 947801384114"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e5ce8b1b-2ec2-450a-b63d-7ee713170281"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801393561","data":{"timestamp":" 947801393561"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e5ce8b1b-2ec2-450a-b63d-7ee713170281"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801409835","data":{"timestamp":" 947801409834"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" 191deb6d-095a-4c46-9fcd-5e2eef881fed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801410067","data":{"timestamp":" 947801410067"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" 191deb6d-095a-4c46-9fcd-5e2eef881fed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801411029","data":{"timestamp":" 947801411029"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" 191deb6d-095a-4c46-9fcd-5e2eef881fed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801412303","data":{"timestamp":" 947801412303"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" 191deb6d-095a-4c46-9fcd-5e2eef881fed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801415212","data":{"timestamp":" 947801415211"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" 191deb6d-095a-4c46-9fcd-5e2eef881fed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801416055","data":{"timestamp":" 947801416055"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" 191deb6d-095a-4c46-9fcd-5e2eef881fed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801416368","data":{"timestamp":" 947801416368"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" 191deb6d-095a-4c46-9fcd-5e2eef881fed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801417602","data":{"timestamp":" 947801417602"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" 191deb6d-095a-4c46-9fcd-5e2eef881fed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801421108","data":{"timestamp":" 947801421108"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" 191deb6d-095a-4c46-9fcd-5e2eef881fed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801422104","data":{"timestamp":" 947801422103"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" 191deb6d-095a-4c46-9fcd-5e2eef881fed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801422369","data":{"timestamp":" 947801422368"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" 191deb6d-095a-4c46-9fcd-5e2eef881fed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801423317","data":{"timestamp":" 947801423316"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" 191deb6d-095a-4c46-9fcd-5e2eef881fed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801426151","data":{"timestamp":" 947801426151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" 191deb6d-095a-4c46-9fcd-5e2eef881fed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801427193","data":{"timestamp":" 947801427193"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" 191deb6d-095a-4c46-9fcd-5e2eef881fed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801427677","data":{"timestamp":" 947801427676"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" 191deb6d-095a-4c46-9fcd-5e2eef881fed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801432259","data":{"timestamp":" 947801432257"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" 191deb6d-095a-4c46-9fcd-5e2eef881fed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801432346","data":{"timestamp":" 947801432346"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" 191deb6d-095a-4c46-9fcd-5e2eef881fed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801440029","data":{"timestamp":" 947801440028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" 191deb6d-095a-4c46-9fcd-5e2eef881fed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..25.off2.18__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801477440","data":{"timestamp":" 947801477439"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" 191deb6d-095a-4c46-9fcd-5e2eef881fed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801490849","data":{"timestamp":" 947801490849"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" 191deb6d-095a-4c46-9fcd-5e2eef881fed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801497133","data":{"timestamp":" 947801497132"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" 191deb6d-095a-4c46-9fcd-5e2eef881fed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801508555","data":{"timestamp":" 947801508555"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801512844","data":{"timestamp":" 947801512844"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801514742","data":{"timestamp":" 947801514742"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801516533","data":{"timestamp":" 947801516533"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801519679","data":{"timestamp":" 947801519679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIANGAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801521303","data":{"timestamp":" 947801521303"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801522961","data":{"timestamp":" 947801522961"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801525975","data":{"timestamp":" 947801525975"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801528604","data":{"timestamp":" 947801528604"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801530953","data":{"timestamp":" 947801530952"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801532673","data":{"timestamp":" 947801532673"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801534811","data":{"timestamp":" 947801534811"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801537124","data":{"timestamp":" 947801537124"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801538912","data":{"timestamp":" 947801538912"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801540936","data":{"timestamp":" 947801540935"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801544107","data":{"timestamp":" 947801544107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801546161","data":{"timestamp":" 947801546161"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKWENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801548028","data":{"timestamp":" 947801548028"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801549691","data":{"timestamp":" 947801549691"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801551542","data":{"timestamp":" 947801551542"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801553693","data":{"timestamp":" 947801553693"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801555415","data":{"timestamp":" 947801555415"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801557599","data":{"timestamp":" 947801557599"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801559620","data":{"timestamp":" 947801559620"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801561167","data":{"timestamp":" 947801561167"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801563063","data":{"timestamp":" 947801563062"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801565107","data":{"timestamp":" 947801565107"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIOKUWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801566939","data":{"timestamp":" 947801566939"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801568677","data":{"timestamp":" 947801568677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801570393","data":{"timestamp":" 947801570393"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila asubuhi walikwenda mbali kwenye mti uliokuwa na matunda matamu ya mkuyu uliokuwa katikati ya mto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801572910","data":{"timestamp":" 947801572910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801574975","data":{"timestamp":" 947801574975"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIRUDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801576456","data":{"timestamp":" 947801576456"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801578344","data":{"timestamp":" 947801578343"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEBEBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801580593","data":{"timestamp":" 947801580593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801582330","data":{"timestamp":" 947801582330"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801584310","data":{"timestamp":" 947801584310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUYU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801587809","data":{"timestamp":" 947801587809"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWALETEA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801589617","data":{"timestamp":" 947801589616"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDUGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801592559","data":{"timestamp":" 947801592559"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha walirudi huku wamebeba matunda ya mkuyu kuwaletea ndugu zao."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801595267","data":{"timestamp":" 947801595267"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOYAONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801597317","data":{"timestamp":" 947801597317"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801599499","data":{"timestamp":" 947801599499"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801601875","data":{"timestamp":" 947801601875"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BUIBUI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801604108","data":{"timestamp":" 947801604108"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANSI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801607035","data":{"timestamp":" 947801607035"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIDONDOKWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801609026","data":{"timestamp":" 947801609026"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801611090","data":{"timestamp":" 947801611090"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alipoyaona matunda hayo Buibui Anansi alidondokwa na mate."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801612952","data":{"timestamp":" 947801612952"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801615450","data":{"timestamp":" 947801615450"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGEWEZAJE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801617729","data":{"timestamp":" 947801617728"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYAPATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801619821","data":{"timestamp":" 947801619821"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801621814","data":{"timestamp":" 947801621814"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je angewezaje kuyapata matunda hayo?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801623722","data":{"timestamp":" 947801623721"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFIKIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801626782","data":{"timestamp":" 947801626782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAFIKIRI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801628589","data":{"timestamp":" 947801628589"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801631025","data":{"timestamp":" 947801631025"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAPATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801633001","data":{"timestamp":" 947801633000"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801634962","data":{"timestamp":" 947801634962"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifikiri akafikiri na akapata wazo zuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZURI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801637321","data":{"timestamp":" 947801637320"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIPAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801639427","data":{"timestamp":" 947801639426"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NTA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801641552","data":{"timestamp":" 947801641552"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAYONATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801643217","data":{"timestamp":" 947801643216"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801645303","data":{"timestamp":" 947801645303"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SEHEMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801647057","data":{"timestamp":" 947801647057"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801648890","data":{"timestamp":" 947801648890"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801650715","data":{"timestamp":" 947801650715"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijipaka nta inayonata kwenye sehemu yake ya nyuma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801653587","data":{"timestamp":" 947801653586"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801656591","data":{"timestamp":" 947801656591"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKACHUKUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801658235","data":{"timestamp":" 947801658235"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIGAE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801660206","data":{"timestamp":" 947801660206"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801662423","data":{"timestamp":" 947801662423"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUNGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801664788","data":{"timestamp":" 947801664788"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801666377","data":{"timestamp":" 947801666377"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801670595","data":{"timestamp":" 947801670595"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801678479","data":{"timestamp":" 947801678478"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801678574","data":{"timestamp":" 947801678574"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..25.off2.18__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801684665","data":{"timestamp":" 947801684665"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801691678","data":{"timestamp":" 947801691677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801697514","data":{"timestamp":" 947801697514"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801704043","data":{"timestamp":" 947801704043"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..25.off2.18__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801709530","data":{"timestamp":" 947801709530"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801716075","data":{"timestamp":" 947801716075"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801721497","data":{"timestamp":" 947801721496"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801728808","data":{"timestamp":" 947801728808"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947801736921","data":{"timestamp":" 947801736921"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000113_234104"," gameId":" e41b0a7d-0b59-422e-b170-fcce68995310"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kisha akachukua kigae cha nyungu akaenda kwa kina kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}